{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"10.0.1","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":1500,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":11,"width":640,"height":480,"responsive":false,"scalable":false,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Text_Caption_331","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_331","title":"Cyber Security August  Safe Surfing Quiz ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_574","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_574","title":"Take our Security Quiz   to test your knowledge.    Click on Begin to start. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_575","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_575","title":"Brought to you by the Information Security Branch  Office of the Chief Information Officer ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_9","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si21887","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si21901","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"Slide21706","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_331","Text_Caption_574","Text_Caption_575","Button_9","si21887","si21901"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide21706"}}},{"id":"si22393","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_725","roles":{}},{"id":"si22301","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_699","title":"1.\tWhat is an example of Clickbait? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22312","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_715","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22316","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_716","title":"A malicious email with an unsettling or urgent message that scares users into clicking on the provided link. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22312_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A malicious email with an unsettling or urgent message that scares users into clicking on the provided link.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22323","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_717","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22327","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_718","title":"A piece of malware that moves a user’s mouse to a desired location on the screen, forcing them to click. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22323_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A piece of malware that moves a user’s mouse to a desired location on the screen, forcing them to click.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24957","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24961","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A clicking sound played through a user’s computer speakers to condition them to click on certain sites over others. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24957_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A clicking sound played through a user’s computer speakers to condition them to click on certain sites over others.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24972","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24976","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"An article or website that uses overtly controversial or alluring headlines, images, or subject matter to entice users into clicking on the provided link. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24972_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"An article or website that uses overtly controversial or alluring headlines, images, or subject matter to entice users into clicking on the provided link.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si22387","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_724","roles":{}},{"id":"si22415","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_107","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22433","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_108","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22455","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_109","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22473","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_110","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22485","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22497","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22509","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22521","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22533","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22545","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22557","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22569","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22582q0","for":"Slide22582q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22357","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_721","title":"Correct - Answer: D  Clickbait often appears in social media (Facebook, Instagram, etc) and attempts to lure users into clicking on links to articles or pages by including provocative, inflammatory, or sexualized language and/or content. Clickbait is almost never an accurate representation of the page users will visit. Best case, it is used to generate views and ad revenue. Worst case, it is used to spread malware.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22369","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_722","title":"Incorrect - Answer: D  Clickbait often appears in social media (Facebook, Instagram, etc) and attempts to lure users into clicking on links to articles or pages by including provocative, inflammatory, or sexualized language and/or content. Clickbait is almost never an accurate representation of the page users will visit. Best case, it is used to generate views and ad revenue. Worst case, it is used to spread malware.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22381","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_723","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22582","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si22301","si22316","si22327","si24961","si24976","si22415","si22433","si22455","si22473","si22485","si22497","si22509","si22521","si22533","si22545","si22557","si22569","si22381"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22582"},"question":{"interactionId":"22281","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"1.\tWhich is the strongest password of the options below?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si26198","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_838","roles":{}},{"id":"si26095","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_795","title":"2.\tYou’ve just signed up for the latest social media page! What should you do first? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26106","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_826","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26110","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_827","title":"Start adding friends/connections and accepting requests. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26106_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_435","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Start adding friends/connections and accepting requests.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si26117","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_828","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26121","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_829","title":"Cruise around on the site and see what’s what. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26117_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_436","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Cruise around on the site and see what’s what.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si26128","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_830","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26132","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_831","title":"Find the privacy and security settings and make sure they are set to your desired level. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26128_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"437","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Find the privacy and security settings and make sure they are set to your desired level.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si26139","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_832","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26143","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_833","title":"Get to work on updating your profile with all your details. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26139_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"439","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Get to work on updating your profile with all your details.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si26192","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_837","roles":{}},{"id":"si26220","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_137","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26238","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_138","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26260","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_139","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26278","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_140","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26290","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26302","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26314","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26326","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26338","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26350","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26362","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26374","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide26387q1","for":"Slide26387q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26162","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_834","title":"Correct  - Answer: C  Social media platforms often start users with very open privacy and security settings, making much of the profile open to view by any other user. Before you do ANYTHING on social media, make sure that you familiarize yourself with the privacy policy, privacy settings, and security settings, and keep them set to the level you want.  For example, some people choose to maintain two accounts: a more secured and private account with personal details for friends and family, and another publicly viewable account with fewer or no personal details for public contests, etc.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26174","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_835","title":"Incorrect  - Answer: C  Social media platforms often start users with very open privacy and security settings, making much of the profile open to view by any other user. Before you do ANYTHING on social media, make sure that you familiarize yourself with the privacy policy, privacy settings, and security settings, and keep them set to the level you want.  For example, some people choose to maintain two accounts: a more secured and private account with personal details for friends and family, and another publicly viewable account with fewer or no personal details for public contests, etc.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26186","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_836","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide26387","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si26095","si26110","si26121","si26132","si26143","si26220","si26238","si26260","si26278","si26290","si26302","si26314","si26326","si26338","si26350","si26362","si26374","si26186"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide26387"},"question":{"interactionId":"26081","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"2.\tYou’ve just signed up for the latest social media page! What should you do first?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["C"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si22716","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_736","roles":{}},{"id":"si22624","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_700","title":"3. True or False: You’re just as safe using the coffee shop Wi-Fi to make an online purchase as you are using your home network. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22635","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_726","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22639","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_727","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22635_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22646","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_728","title":" ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22650","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_729","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22646_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si22710","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_735","roles":{}},{"id":"si22738","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_111","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22756","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_112","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22778","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_113","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22796","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_114","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22808","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22820","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22832","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22844","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22856","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22868","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22880","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22892","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide22905q2","for":"Slide22905q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22680","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_732","title":"Correct  -  Answer: False  It’s always best to use your home network to conduct any transactions where you are providing personal or payment information over the internet. It is much easier to have your information intercepted or compromised when using a (potentially) poorly-secured network with possibly malicious users (other coffee shop “customers”). If you MUST use a public or company Wi-Fi connection to conduct personal or business transactions, consider using a VPN service to encrypt your data and protect yourself from having your information stolen.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22692","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_733","title":"Incorrect  -  Answer: False  It’s always best to use your home network to conduct any transactions where you are providing personal or payment information over the internet. It is much easier to have your information intercepted or compromised when using a (potentially) poorly-secured network with possibly malicious users (other coffee shop “customers”). If you MUST use a public or company Wi-Fi connection to conduct personal or business transactions, consider using a VPN service to encrypt your data and protect yourself from having your information stolen.   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si22704","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_734","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide22905","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si22624","si22639","si22650","si22738","si22756","si22778","si22796","si22808","si22820","si22832","si22844","si22856","si22868","si22880","si22892","si22704"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide22905"},"question":{"interactionId":"22604","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"3. True or False: You’re just as safe using the coffee shop Wi-Fi to make an online purchase as you are using your home network.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["2"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si26864","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_864","roles":{}},{"id":"si26761","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_801","title":"4. Of the following example social media posts, which should you NEVER respond to? (Check all that apply) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26772","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_852","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26776","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_853","title":"What’s your 30’s gangster name? (First name – your first pet, Last name – the street you grew up on) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26776","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide27053q3"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si26772_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"What’s your 30’s gangster name? (First name – your first pet, Last name – the street you grew up on)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si26783","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_854","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26787","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_855","title":"Who else is a February baby? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26787","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide27053q3"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si26783_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Who else is a February baby?\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si26794","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_856","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26798","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_857","title":"Hands up if you grew up in a small town. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26798","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide27053q3"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si26794_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Hands up if you grew up in a small town.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si26805","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_858","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26809","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_859","title":"Pick your birth month to reveal your dominant trait. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26809","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide27053q3"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si26805_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Pick your birth month to reveal your dominant trait.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si26858","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_863","roles":{}},{"id":"si26886","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_145","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26904","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_146","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26926","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_147","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26944","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_148","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26956","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26968","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26980","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26992","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27004","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27016","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27028","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27040","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide27053q3","for":"Slide27053q3"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26828","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_860","title":"Correct  - Answer: A,B,C,D  All of the above answers are examples of social engineering. Social engineering is the psychological manipulation of people into performing actions or divulging confidential information. In this case, it leverages the desire of people to participate or be validated to get people to give up common password reset security questions. (i.e. You just gave a cybercriminal your first pet’s name, which is also the password reset question for your bank…)  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26840","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_861","title":"Incorrect  - Answer: A,B,C,D  All of the above answers are examples of social engineering. Social engineering is the psychological manipulation of people into performing actions or divulging confidential information. In this case, it leverages the desire of people to participate or be validated to get people to give up common password reset security questions. (i.e. You just gave a cybercriminal your first pet’s name, which is also the password reset question for your bank…)  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si26852","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_862","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide27053","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si26761","si26776","si26787","si26798","si26809","si26886","si26904","si26926","si26944","si26956","si26968","si26980","si26992","si27004","si27016","si27028","si27040","si26852"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide27053"},"question":{"interactionId":"26747","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"4. Of the following example social media posts, which should you NEVER respond to? (Check all that apply)\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A","B","C","D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":10}}}},{"id":"si27197","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_877","roles":{}},{"id":"si27094","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_802","title":"5. What is “malvertising”? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27105","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_865","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27109","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_866","title":"Intrusive actions from webpage / in-app advertisements that lead a user to navigate to an unintended webpage or download an unwanted or malicious program. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27105_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"457","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Intrusive actions from webpage / in-app advertisements that lead a user to navigate to an unintended webpage or download an unwanted or malicious program.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si27116","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_867","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27120","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_868","title":"A browser hijack that causes all ads to be replaced by images of Nathan Fillion from Firefly. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27116_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"459","roles":{"answer":{"title":"A browser hijack that causes all ads to be replaced by images of Nathan Fillion from Firefly.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si27127","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_869","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27131","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_870","title":"Advertising that is lewd or in poor taste. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27127_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"461","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Advertising that is lewd or in poor taste.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si27138","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_871","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27142","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_872","title":"Unsolicited emails advertising unwanted items ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27138_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"463","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Unsolicited emails advertising unwanted items\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si27191","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_876","roles":{}},{"id":"si27219","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_149","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27237","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_150","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27259","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_151","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27277","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_152","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27289","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27301","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27313","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27325","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27337","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27349","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27361","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27373","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide27386q4","for":"Slide27386q4"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27161","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_873","title":"Correct  -  Answer: A  Malvertising is a relatively new form of malware attack that involves transmitting malware to users via corrupted or malicious advertisements. Cybercriminals may exploit weaknesses of advertising platforms to infect legitimate ads with malware, or they submit malicious ads to internet ad companies which go undetected and are passed along to users. These ads tend to either trick users into downloading malicious programs or redirect them to malicious pages. A good defense against malvertising is to install ad-blocking software. This could be either a standalone app, or a browser-based solution (e.g. Chrome extension, Firefox add-on, etc)   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27173","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_874","title":"Incorrect  -  Answer: A  Malvertising is a relatively new form of malware attack that involves transmitting malware to users via corrupted or malicious advertisements. Cybercriminals may exploit weaknesses of advertising platforms to infect legitimate ads with malware, or they submit malicious ads to internet ad companies which go undetected and are passed along to users. These ads tend to either trick users into downloading malicious programs or redirect them to malicious pages. A good defense against malvertising is to install ad-blocking software. This could be either a standalone app, or a browser-based solution (e.g. Chrome extension, Firefox add-on, etc)   Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27185","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_875","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide27386","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si27094","si27109","si27120","si27131","si27142","si27219","si27237","si27259","si27277","si27289","si27301","si27313","si27325","si27337","si27349","si27361","si27373","si27185"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide27386"},"question":{"interactionId":"27080","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"5. What is “malvertising”?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":10}}}},{"id":"si23482","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_763","roles":{}},{"id":"si23379","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_750","title":"6. What are some useful features to look for in a password manager? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23390","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_751","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23394","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_752","title":"Multi-factor Authentication (MFA) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23390_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_407","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Multi-factor Authentication (MFA)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23401","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_753","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23405","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_754","title":"Random Password Generator ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23401_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_408","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Random Password Generator\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si27462","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27466","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multi platform support (e.g. PC, Android, and iOS) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27462_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Multi platform support (e.g. PC, Android, and iOS)\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si27477","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27481","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"All of the above ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27477_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"All of the above\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si23476","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_762","roles":{}},{"id":"si23504","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_119","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23522","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_120","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23544","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_121","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23562","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_122","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23574","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23586","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23598","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23610","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23622","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23634","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23646","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23658","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide23671q5","for":"Slide23671q5"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23446","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_759","title":"Correct  - Answer: D  Password managers are increasingly popular tools that securely store very complex and strong passwords for users, allowing them use every password on file, while only having to remember one master password.   Features to look for include: Multi-factor authentication, which prompts you to confirm your identity on a secondary device / account to login Random password generators, which generate extraordinarily long and complex passwords to maximize security, and Multi-platform support, which enables you to use the same password manager on different devices such as your home PC and your smart phone at the same time.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23458","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_760","title":"Incorrect  - Answer: D  Password managers are increasingly popular tools that securely store very complex and strong passwords for users, allowing them use every password on file, while only having to remember one master password.   Features to look for include: Multi-factor authentication, which prompts you to confirm your identity on a secondary device / account to login Random password generators, which generate extraordinarily long and complex passwords to maximize security, and Multi-platform support, which enables you to use the same password manager on different devices such as your home PC and your smart phone at the same time.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23470","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_761","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide23671","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si23379","si23394","si23405","si27466","si27481","si23504","si23522","si23544","si23562","si23574","si23586","si23598","si23610","si23622","si23634","si23646","si23658","si23470"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide23671"},"question":{"interactionId":"23359","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"6. What are some useful features to look for in a password manager?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si23820","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_777","roles":{}},{"id":"si23717","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_764","title":"7. You looked up the price of an airline ticket to go to an upcoming family gathering, and now your social media page is full of ads for dream vacation getaways. What’s the best choice of the below options to stop seeing these ads? ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23728","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_765","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23732","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_766","title":"Stop using social media. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23728_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Stop using social media.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23739","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_767","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23743","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_768","title":"Clear your browser cache and cookies. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23739_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Clear your browser cache and cookies.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si23750","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_769","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23754","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_770","title":"Write an angry email to the airlines featured in the ads. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23750_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Write an angry email to the airlines featured in the ads.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si24830","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24834","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Log out of your social media account and log back in. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si24830_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Log out of your social media account and log back in.\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si23814","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_776","roles":{}},{"id":"si23842","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_123","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23860","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_124","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23882","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_125","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23900","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_126","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23912","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23924","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23936","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23948","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23960","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23972","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23984","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23996","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide24009q6","for":"Slide24009q6"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23784","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_773","title":"Correct  -  Answer: B  Knowing how to clear your browser cache and cookies is an important skill to have. Many webpages leave behind a small packet of data called a “cookie” on your device when you are browsing. This file contains information about your activity on the page which allows advertisers to target ads from their library to you. Depending on the advertiser, these ads can often persist across many pages. So while quitting social media may seem like an effective (and perhaps extreme) step, if you don’t remove the internet cookie saying you visited an airline page, you will likely see more vacation ads popping up as you continue to browse the internet.    Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23796","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_774","title":"Incorrect  -  Answer: B  Knowing how to clear your browser cache and cookies is an important skill to have. Many webpages leave behind a small packet of data called a “cookie” on your device when you are browsing. This file contains information about your activity on the page which allows advertisers to target ads from their library to you. Depending on the advertiser, these ads can often persist across many pages. So while quitting social media may seem like an effective (and perhaps extreme) step, if you don’t remove the internet cookie saying you visited an airline page, you will likely see more vacation ads popping up as you continue to browse the internet.    Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si23808","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_775","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide24009","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si23717","si23732","si23743","si23754","si24834","si23842","si23860","si23882","si23900","si23912","si23924","si23936","si23948","si23960","si23972","si23984","si23996","si23808"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide24009"},"question":{"interactionId":"23697","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"7. Which age group is most likely to use a different password for each account?\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si25607","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_825","roles":{}},{"id":"si25493","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_794","title":"8. True or false: Around the world, over 350,000 new pieces of malware are detected every day. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25504","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_811","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25508","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_812","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25504_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"175_429","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si25515","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_813","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25519","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_814","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25515_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"179_430","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si25601","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_824","roles":{}},{"id":"si25629","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_133","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25647","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_134","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25669","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_135","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25687","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_136","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25699","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25711","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Submit ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25723","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25735","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25747","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25759","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":">> ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeNext","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25771","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25783","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"<< ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"reviewModeBack","question":"Slide25796q7","for":"Slide25796q7"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25571","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_821","title":"Correct  -  Answer: True  The AV-test institute registers over 350,000 NEW malicious programs (malware) and potentially unwanted applications (PUA) a day. With the daily emergence of new threats, it’s important to have a reliable anti-virus program installed on your devices and keep it up to date.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25583","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_822","title":"Incorrect  -  Answer: True  The AV-test institute registers over 350,000 NEW malicious programs (malware) and potentially unwanted applications (PUA) a day. With the daily emergence of new threats, it’s important to have a reliable anti-virus program installed on your devices and keep it up to date.  Press anwhere or click ‘y’ to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si25595","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_823","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide25796","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si25493","si25508","si25519","si25629","si25647","si25669","si25687","si25699","si25711","si25723","si25735","si25747","si25759","si25771","si25783","si25595"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide25796"},"question":{"interactionId":"25473","quizId":458,"title":"Multiple Choice","text":"8. True or false: Around the world, over 350,000 new pieces of malware are detected every day.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_107","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_107","title":"Quiz Results ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6083","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si27503","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6079","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Total Questions: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6103","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si6107","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si6121","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20489","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20502","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Continue ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"continue","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20517","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si20530","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Review Quiz ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"review","question":"","for":""},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si27499","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" Your Correct Answers: ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6038","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":[],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6038"}}},{"id":"si6231","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_4","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19054","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si19068","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_9","title":"Stay Current With Information Security By Subscribing to the:   Weekly Security News Digest ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_298","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_298","title":"Thank you for taking the quiz.  To exit the quiz, close the browser window. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide6219","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si6231","Button_4","si19054","si19068","SmartShape_9","Text_Caption_298"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":600},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide6219"}}},{"id":"Pool502","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":502,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"Aug2021Quiz","class":"project","title":"Aug2021Quiz","children":["Slide21706","Slide22582","Slide26387","Slide22905","Slide27053","Slide27386","Slide23671","Slide24009","Slide25796","Slide6038","Slide6219"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":458,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide22582q0","Slide26387q1","Slide22905q2","Slide27053q3","Slide27386q4","Slide23671q5","Slide24009q6","Slide25796q7"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":80,"passScore":64}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide21706","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide22582","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide26387","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide22905","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide27053","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide27386","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide23671","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide24009","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide25796","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide6038","title":"Slide 10"},{"id":"Slide6219","title":"Slide 11"}]}